[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael and Ryan"]}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ":", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "But this French swimmer Yannick Agnel has really taken the scruff of the neck of the swimming competition and changed the whole game, hasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "French", "swimmer", "Yannick", "Agnel", "has", "really", "taken", "the", "scruff", "of", "the", "neck", "of", "the", "swimming", "competition", "and", "changed", "the", "whole", "game", ",", "has", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, I think all of us have been captivated about -- talking about Michael and Ryan, and there's the rest of the world that has a lot talent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "all", "of", "us", "have", "been", "captivated", "about", "--", "talking", "about", "Michael", "and", "Ryan", ",", "and", "there", "'s", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "world", "that", "has", "a", "lot", "talent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Yannick Agnel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Should Phelps have basically quilt after Beijing on the ultimate high?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "Phelps", "have", "basically", "quilt", "after", "Beijing", "on", "the", "ultimate", "high", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "There's so much money in this.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "so", "much", "money", "in", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beijing"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't want to speculate on anything that would be negative to her performance.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "want", "to", "speculate", "on", "anything", "that", "would", "be", "negative", "to", "her", "performance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billions of dollars"], "ORGANIZATION": ["International Olympic Committee"]}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Given social media now as it is, do you think it's time that NBC bit the bullet and began to broadcast the big stuff live?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "social", "media", "now", "as", "it", "is", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "time", "that", "NBC", "bit", "the", "bullet", "and", "began", "to", "broadcast", "the", "big", "stuff", "live", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I think that they're in sort of a quandary about this because they actually bid for the Olympic Games a number of years ago and paid the International Olympic Committee billions of dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "they", "'re", "in", "sort", "of", "a", "quandary", "about", "this", "because", "they", "actually", "bid", "for", "the", "Olympic", "Games", "a", "number", "of", "years", "ago", "and", "paid", "the", "International", "Olympic", "Committee", "billions", "of", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What was the first thing he said to you afterwards?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "first", "thing", "he", "said", "to", "you", "afterwards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "He gave me his flowers.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "gave", "me", "his", "flowers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Oh you haven't?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", "you", "have", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "No, I've only seen him from far away.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "only", "seen", "him", "from", "far", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "It's about being honest, tough love?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "being", "honest", ",", "tough", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "I've always been honest with all my kids.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "always", "been", "honest", "with", "all", "my", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Who would be the right kind of woman for your boy?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "the", "right", "kind", "of", "woman", "for", "your", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "They have to be a family loving person that could stand having a large family and crazy family at that.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "to", "be", "a", "family", "loving", "person", "that", "could", "stand", "having", "a", "large", "family", "and", "crazy", "family", "at", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "That apparently he cries at movies and stuff like that, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "apparently", "he", "cries", "at", "movies", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "OCHTE: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["OCHTE", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "So that makes him instantly more lovable to women, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "makes", "him", "instantly", "more", "lovable", "to", "women", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Yes, he's very caring and loves kids.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "'s", "very", "caring", "and", "loves", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What did you make of it as his mother?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "as", "his", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "It's Ryan.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "Ryan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "You prefer him not to, would you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "prefer", "him", "not", "to", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Are they anxious to see it in real time on television?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "anxious", "to", "see", "it", "in", "real", "time", "on", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Yes, but we call all our family and we tell them how they did immediately.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "we", "call", "all", "our", "family", "and", "we", "tell", "them", "how", "they", "did", "immediately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "I think sports has to be live, doesn't it, it on TV?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "sports", "has", "to", "be", "live", ",", "does", "n't", "it", ",", "it", "on", "TV", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "So how are you feeling?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "are", "you", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, I feel all right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "feel", "all", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Tired?", "question_tokens": ["Tired", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "No, not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "You get that, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "get", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, you also warned me, you've been answering questions all day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "also", "warned", "me", ",", "you", "'ve", "been", "answering", "questions", "all", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "And what do you feel about that responsibility?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "responsibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "I mean, sometimes I feel it, but, I mean, I like to just think of myself as a normal person who just has a passion, has a goal and a dream and goes out and does it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "sometimes", "I", "feel", "it", ",", "but", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "like", "to", "just", "think", "of", "myself", "as", "a", "normal", "person", "who", "just", "has", "a", "passion", ",", "has", "a", "goal", "and", "a", "dream", "and", "goes", "out", "and", "does", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What do you consider normal?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "consider", "normal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, not spending 20 years in the pool.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "spending", "20", "years", "in", "the", "pool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Do you know anybody else that has done that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "anybody", "else", "that", "has", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What is the motivation at the end of the day for that kind of extreme dedication?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "motivation", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", "for", "that", "kind", "of", "extreme", "dedication", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "I mean, if you want to be the best, you have to do things that other people aren't willing to do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "want", "to", "be", "the", "best", ",", "you", "have", "to", "do", "things", "that", "other", "people", "are", "n't", "willing", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "What were the young Michael Phelps dreams?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "young", "Michael", "Phelps", "dreams", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Olympic gold medalist.", "answer_tokens": ["Olympic", "gold", "medalist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "From what age did you know that?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "age", "did", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I mean, I grew up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "grew", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "When you're at home playing, do you play board games together?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "at", "home", "playing", ",", "do", "you", "play", "board", "games", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "I would always try to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "always", "try", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jordan"]}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "Who are your sporting idols?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "your", "sporting", "idols", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Michael Jordan.", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "Jordan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Why him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "He changed the sport of basketball in my eyes.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "changed", "the", "sport", "of", "basketball", "in", "my", "eyes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I haven't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "What would you ask him if you were able to meet Michael Jordan?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "ask", "him", "if", "you", "were", "able", "to", "meet", "Michael", "Jordan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I've -- you know, I've had that thought a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "that", "thought", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jordan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "What's the thing you're most curious about with him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "thing", "you", "'re", "most", "curious", "about", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I mean I think part of me would ask him about what made him come back to the sport.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "think", "part", "of", "me", "would", "ask", "him", "about", "what", "made", "him", "come", "back", "to", "the", "sport", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "How have you dealt with that side of things?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "dealt", "with", "that", "side", "of", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "You know I'm sure I'll be the first one to admit I've made a lot of mistakes in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "'m", "sure", "I", "'ll", "be", "the", "first", "one", "to", "admit", "I", "'ve", "made", "a", "lot", "of", "mistakes", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "When you knew that picture was coming out, how did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "knew", "that", "picture", "was", "coming", "out", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Not too good.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "too", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "RB", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "I mean, did you feel -- what is that feeling like?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "did", "you", "feel", "--", "what", "is", "that", "feeling", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Like the worst in the world, you know, like I lost all the -- I mean, I think it sort of just -- yes, it's terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "the", "worst", "in", "the", "world", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "I", "lost", "all", "the", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "it", "sort", "of", "just", "--", "yes", ",", "it", "'s", "terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "How did you brace yourself for that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "brace", "yourself", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "You know I think -- my mom has always been obviously how all moms are.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "think", "--", "my", "mom", "has", "always", "been", "obviously", "how", "all", "moms", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Do you feel people overreacting?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "people", "overreacting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Yes, I did, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Have you found you've got more attractive the more gold medals you won?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "found", "you", "'ve", "got", "more", "attractive", "the", "more", "gold", "medals", "you", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "DT", "RBR", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I think the biggest thing is you got to find who's real and who's not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "biggest", "thing", "is", "you", "got", "to", "find", "who", "'s", "real", "and", "who", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "With what?", "question_tokens": ["With", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I was assuming a woman.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "assuming", "a", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Have you had your heart broken?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "your", "heart", "broken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Sure definitely probably, high school.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "definitely", "probably", ",", "high", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "A race you really wanted to win?", "question_tokens": ["A", "race", "you", "really", "wanted", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I mean, I think they're both learning experiences.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "both", "learning", "experiences", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Does winning that gold medal repeatedly come above everything else?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "winning", "that", "gold", "medal", "repeatedly", "come", "above", "everything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "For me it's more about personal goals and things I want to achieve myself.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", "it", "'s", "more", "about", "personal", "goals", "and", "things", "I", "want", "to", "achieve", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "That will be it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "will", "be", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Will you still swim a lot for fun?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "still", "swim", "a", "lot", "for", "fun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Probably going to need to do something for exercise.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "going", "to", "need", "to", "do", "something", "for", "exercise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Is swimming still fun for you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "swimming", "still", "fun", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "You could imagine just doing laps for no reason?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "imagine", "just", "doing", "laps", "for", "no", "reason", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I think one of the biggest things after I do retire is, you know, now when I go to the ocean, go to the beach, I don't want get in the water.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "biggest", "things", "after", "I", "do", "retire", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "now", "when", "I", "go", "to", "the", "ocean", ",", "go", "to", "the", "beach", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "get", "in", "the", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What have you found makes or can make a difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "found", "makes", "or", "can", "make", "a", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I mean, the biggest thing is -- I talk about how I got to where I am, a dream, a plan and I reach for it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "biggest", "thing", "is", "--", "I", "talk", "about", "how", "I", "got", "to", "where", "I", "am", ",", "a", "dream", ",", "a", "plan", "and", "I", "reach", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Do you protect it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "protect", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "There are things that are protected, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "things", "that", "are", "protected", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What was going through your mind through that period?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "through", "that", "period", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Do you feel now as motivated as you've ever been?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "now", "as", "motivated", "as", "you", "'ve", "ever", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I mean, I wouldn't say it was as motivated as I've ever been.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "it", "was", "as", "motivated", "as", "I", "'ve", "ever", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "How many medals, do you know how many you've won?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "medals", ",", "do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "you", "'ve", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Sixteen.", "answer_tokens": ["Sixteen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "A bit of doubt about this, you actually know where they are?", "question_tokens": ["A", "bit", "of", "doubt", "about", "this", ",", "you", "actually", "know", "where", "they", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps"]}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How would you like to be remembered whatever happens in London?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "whatever", "happens", "in", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Being the first Michael Phelps that's really the only thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "the", "first", "Michael", "Phelps", "that", "'s", "really", "the", "only", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "First of all, are you enjoying the games?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "are", "you", "enjoying", "the", "games", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Enormously.", "answer_tokens": ["Enormously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "So what do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "In fact, what I heard from Mitt Romney and it was great to see it said so clearly.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "fact", ",", "what", "I", "heard", "from", "Mitt", "Romney", "and", "it", "was", "great", "to", "see", "it", "said", "so", "clearly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Jerusalem"]}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "If you become president of the United States, would you move the U.S. embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "become", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "would", "you", "move", "the", "U.S.", "embassy", "from", "Tel", "Aviv", "to", "Jerusalem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I think it's long been the policy of our country to ultimately have our embassy in the nation's capital of Jerusalem.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "long", "been", "the", "policy", "of", "our", "country", "to", "ultimately", "have", "our", "embassy", "in", "the", "nation", "'s", "capital", "of", "Jerusalem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "U.S.", "Tel Aviv", "Jerusalem"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Is that your view?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I think it's absolutely true.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "absolutely", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Were you disappointed with that?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "disappointed", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "We were disappointed.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "disappointed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "How old are you for goodness sakes?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "are", "you", "for", "goodness", "sakes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "I'm 33.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "33", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Does it get any less exciting, less enjoyable?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "get", "any", "less", "exciting", ",", "less", "enjoyable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "VBG", ",", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "How do you feel representing America and doing so for such a long period of time?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "representing", "America", "and", "doing", "so", "for", "such", "a", "long", "period", "of", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Well, you know, it's such an honor.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "such", "an", "honor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "As someone as a professional marksman, what do you think about the whole debate that's raging about gun control and so on?", "question_tokens": ["As", "someone", "as", "a", "professional", "marksman", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "whole", "debate", "that", "'s", "raging", "about", "gun", "control", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Well, you know, obviously, my heart goes out for the victims and their families and it's really sad this even occurred.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "obviously", ",", "my", "heart", "goes", "out", "for", "the", "victims", "and", "their", "families", "and", "it", "'s", "really", "sad", "this", "even", "occurred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]